yeah
oh no I gotta sign something again so
much signing all right we're good or
that in there looks good
cool don't you do me a big favor
what's up you will be see the survey
from Toyota yeah all right all right
perfect
I understand there you go new car
delivered I have as you go excellent yes
oh we got some people talking in chat we
got a brand new
excellent thank you very much Steven
have a good day
if you guys didn't see this were at the
world's largest toyota dealership right
now long ago Toyota
welcome welcome well I'm so happy I
tried to stream like three times and
then I rebooted my phone and then it
worked so twitch made it work you know
this is my friend Tom he's gonna be
holding the camera for you guys while we
install open pilot on this brand-new
Corolla that we just got from the
dealership right we gotta get out of you
let's get out of here let's go let's go
let's coach whichis let's go let's go
all right all right
quite apart spy camera
this car is literally brand new how much
miles does it happen we have fourteen
point two miles on us show on the miles
how do I sweat you oh you can switch it
with that there we go perfect
yeah so it's a brand new Corolla right
here all right first he posts a pixel of
Ferrari on the gram the dreams of the
Corolla you ever hear of a
bait-and-switch guys all right you think
we could find any parking spot with
shade I mean it's like I'm bad with
these you know it's actually kind of
good just barking like a general let's
go all right
all right so guys I'll show you this
guy's super confused look at his face
he's like what the fuck are you doing
you're not this isn't child friendly no
no no this is not no but this is a
Christian channel so Oh Christian
channel so you know don't blaspheme the
name of Jesus all right so this is legit
a brand new 2020 Toyota Corolla xse we
got the top trim with the fake leather
seat glad I got the PAP it's brand new
oh yeah they got look at this thank you
for coming in you know lonely take
sapphire far guys it was terrible
Vicky's keys are stole in the back these
are in the bag this is the legit brand
new car all right
so in the trunk I have a backpack and in
the backpack
I have some stuff that I purchased at
become a I shop that's at shop comma
Dada Y you can go buy everything that
I'm about to show off in this stream I
swear it's not an it's it's still an ad
if it's your own company and they don't
pay you know
although it's not as nicely packaged as
the one you'll buy we have some stuff
right here and beyond decorative this is
a common power they're $20 and they help
power your giraffe I thought there are
pandas don't know we have Hanna next is
enjoy app these are $60 you plug the
power into the giraffe the power looks a
whole lot like a panda it does look like
a panda but it says powered all I see
okay I can't move Han so this is
actually a pair to consist paintball I
see this is a giraffe so your power goes
in this giraffe all put your power in
that draft guys your panda goes in this
giraffe hole now you say like why don't
you do that at the factory and the
answer is we should it's gonna charge $1
right we have some mounts right here so
I can mount my e onto my windshield and
of course we have a comma a ie on right
here I'm afraid it might be dead
which would be terrible but I don't look
that right good so guys what are the
odds that it's just gonna work out of
the box love because this is a brand new
Toyota Corolla that's not even supported
yet you know the pilot we're gonna try
our best to make it work and now the
long part of the street starts let's see
how long it's gonna take you to get this
set up
alright so it's like that mount on there
like that
that's looking pretty good this thing
moved up
then let's take the trip off right here
this piece comes right off like that I
swear this is a brand new car guys this
piece they're saying you should have
khamenei I speedruns
[Music]
I look at that glove box no space no so
many manuals wait does that curl a
hybrid man you wanted buy a Corolla
hybrid all right so we're loading up
open pilot right here it's got to build
the latest stuff and so some of you guys
think you have to be really careful
about where you stick their young the
truth is you don't because all the
calibration is incredible and automatic
so it's not like China Center kind of
yeah that's utter no that's not so no no
they've done every Center with the car
it just has to be like oriented around
go do I have enough space to slide it
now that seems perfect I did it cost
he paid two thousand dollars he's quite
a good negotiator for the Corolla yeah
you can get these things super cheap
super cheap use that no negotiate it was
like mm like 240 whatever we like to
give them a little bit of a useful tip
so guys um first thing to do when you're
negotiating for cars ask to see the
invoice
and the invoice stick the car dealership
will tell you but this is what we paid
for the car man come on we can't sell
any food less than that then we don't
make money they do use what's called
hold back Toyota has a 2% hold back so
it's about 600 of the car so you want to
get a car about four hundred below
invoice essentially they just sold you
the car for $180 bra pretty much that's
pretty much what they made but like I
said we aren't the largest Richie in the
parking lot like chef guest parking and
shit all right
cool we have some okay so let me show
you guys how easy it is now to just
install this common equipment here I'm
just gonna take this wire don't unplug
it I'm gonna plug this wire into here
and then click that up into there and
then we're good all right we've got a
bunch of malfunctions but that's okay we
love malfunction Coast fair about to be
fixed as soon as we install open fire
all right so now my Panda has power
just gonna rouse this coma power down
here that goes into a convenient
we gotta get down there on this one
okay someone goes doesn't appreciate it
you never you don't drive it off a lock
[Laughter]
huh no no no this is crazy today I have
an obd and check if the 20/20 coral has
an obd2 port oh where it looks like it
should be some cars have them on the
console oh it's just detached that's it
- it's there wow it's ernie out well
that's kind of a scam this car is
falling apart it legitimately like the
over--he part was like popped out of its
thing
all right well so much for that
legendary Toyota build quality
alright let's just shove in this cup of
power right here
this alright we are comma power good to
go alright that's plugged in now we just
got to take our USB cable connect it
right here from this little panda
over around back here so inside the role
is our disposable car 31 all right
just from this in the front so we don't
get the table in the hammer all right
how do you know if it works we just have
to turn like some of these switches like
those two or something oh god there's
like four switches here and even though
I like design this product I don't know
which switch to flip but maybe we did it
right let's try uh-huh
no wait wait wait give the seconds go
build things
well now now it didn't work
should be good
here is the switch
switch
all the switches
just don't seem to matter at all
and not flashed her something
it says panda active no matter what I'm
an alter-ego alright well that's an SSH
into the ER guys so a common a I we are
trying our best to make this stuff as
convenient and user-friendly as possible
but some time of course we fall short
but that won't stop us from trying
let's wouldn't it be great if that was
all we had to do that would be amazing
yeah now we're gonna be here for another
30 minutes because we've gotta figure
out how they like SSH in and have a
fingerprint and bullshit right but don't
worry we'll call Comi and I support all
one who support how I you know what will
go on discord will log on to the comma a
discord will say hi I'm a new user and I
need help setting up no one's gonna help
you it's Sunday nobody will know what is
it what are the twitch chat people
saying
do they like this stream so far me
people got 233 holy shit that's a lot of
people we got to do a good job they all
they all keep saying Joe Rogan oh no I
told them no yeah you have a Joe Rogan
Army move little people I know Joe Rogan
wait why is this a payment oh now it
says nope and okay so well not
unplugging the pandan this is panda
active oh wow very respectful someone
said thank you for declining thank you
for declining yes of course you know the
kind of person I'm alright let's try
this this should go into cars started
I'm not sure why it isn't doing that
giraffe is properly seated
guys already broken
walk back MBA hey think something's
wrong with the software I'm certain
you've had this for five minutes
what do you wait so I sir I've never
seen this before this switch is what's
connecting so that switches what does
this started
this switch is something else George
someone said hurry up because it's 3
a.m. and he needs to go to sleep oh ok
ok you really got hurry up now man yo
he's got a sleep laptop that we always
keep in the car with us they're saying
it's gonna die before it leaves law
[Laughter]
laptop that we always carry with us and
we go in here to settings and then we
are guys like this is really live see
that's the difference between my twitch
gym and other people's twitch streams um
a lot of people like you know pre
rehearse what they're gonna do I
wouldn't do that we make it up as we go
along
alright turning hotspot on
or she keeps reminding you he's got a
sleep man Wow shit
right
so we're right here on the laptop we're
gonna connect to wheedle they're all
named wheedle have two Pokemon someone
keeps posting an X an excerpt from your
own a little violin thing about the
draftsmen oh yes make sure that your app
switches it's gonna go in a second one
oh I should turn to off I actually think
I don't want three on because I have a
comma power so we definitely want the
frc connected to the perfect that's good
goals when you're twitch streamers know
more about your products than you oh you
know they have the Internet so they're
cheating it's going to terminal here
zero zero zero zero open pilot no
resistor comma zero one zero one open
pilot resistor comma power oh wait a
second do we not have a resistor no but
that shouldn't affect whether the
started line works see what I'm confused
about is why this isn't even detecting
that the car was started it should
but that's confusing to me
all right well it's given an IP address
maybe we can show on the screen that
works at all alright so we're gonna give
you the IP address
we're gonna say um but you know there
really is our goal at comma to be much
better about this out of box experience
right now I can't connect to a host
phone network oh did you try that
someone said just just try saying I'm in
I mean yeah like like do you type
something and go on in and I think it
works
oh that's what we see your movies oh
that's a fair point yeah yeah I usually
say yeah yeah but you know the problem
of movies is they got like script ideas
and shit I know long ago guest
einat's perfect wait but how come I
can't connect to wheedle I was connected
to read only oh we don't write well you
just conveniently reboot your phone
right there um see guys one thing I
promise that we will never do Akane eye
is lie to you he broke the wheedle we're
not lying the wheedle broken have you
tried booting without obd connected
might be newer outies where obd
disconnects unless out ii can bridge
enabled director home we'll set that we
have our stuff properly installed for
some reason the panda just isn't
detecting a started signal
which is interesting
but as soon as we get into the wheedle
we'll be good you got any master balls
no dammit oh yeah they're they're back
at the office you know wait but this is
really what if this doesn't work did I
break this e on some now okay open
tethering settings
portable Wi-Fi hotspot' on
okay acting perfect it's now I can doing
my laptop we connect to the Nissan Wi-Fi
- oh it really isn't talking to the
Panda because I see the pandas pandas
Wi-Fi here and open pilots should
automatically disable that if it was
working so we don't actually run in
public open pilot we run a special
internal version of a pod and there's a
chance that's also what's causing the
problem
if somebody in CI is something somebody
broke if somebody broke commas build you
have engineers that are known for
occasionally breaking builds a lot
better about that we started really
using like CI and stuff I don't
understand why I can't even ping it oh
this isn't the right IPA no no that's
the internal IP what's the public IP
avidians
does anyone know I'm sure they can look
that up anyone know the public IP of an
yacht someone said check your Trello
check my Trello
a trowel oh this is like like shit it's
supposed to like someone said one 19000
I think yeah no no I think I got it
it's one into one six eight dot
twenty-three dot one okay so now let's
SSH in on four uh-huh
okay now I'm getting permission denied
for the key you know
all right so we're just gonna have to oh
you want to turn your hotspot on yeah
yeah so if I can get data you got rekt
me on no no no none that I need to
download like 2k of stuff
my server
I can't connect to their guests in her
top tiles the passwords right there we
won't show to be twitchy's
perfect alright we're on the internet so
let's go here let's just SSH into my
computer back at home
no mine ssh over hot spots oh yeah that
was happening to me at sometimes hot
spots
get fucked oh shit I don't even know how
to get the
all right we'll just make sure SSH is
enabled the problem is I don't think our
reruns use the public key or maybe they
do let's say wait so now I can't even
get on the Internet
got a github calm
connected sure
works
maybe DNS
oh well
oh we could go drives that Starbucks
right there oh you wanna drive that
Starbucks
yeah well another sporting spot up there
would actually just go to the Starbucks
download the key and then come back here
I think you can park afar the Starbucks
and just download the key we can try not
to write there yeah let's go 85 guys
what if we fail we really might okay
let's go to the Starbucks
it's the dealership Starbucks this is
the largest car dealership in the world
they have a subway and a Starbucks and
they are very proud of their stuff look
subway at Starbucks the sales man
compared it to their own tiny small town
there's their tiny small town they're
very excited about all the obvious it's
just not connecting to the Panda person
this might be an easier problem than we
think I might just be able to take the
Panda
you know what I have in my backpack walk
I have a USBC to a converter and I can
flash the Panda right here for my
convenient computer maybe that's the
problem maybe the problem is just in
panda flashing there so I have a park
over here I don't think every used car
by the Starbucks they're gonna try to
sell my Corolla they're gonna try to buy
now they're gonna try to buy irinka
trade it in all I think you can work
here yeah they're gonna think you're
like a terrorist or something about
young kids sitting in his car outside
with the other cyber terror that's a bit
of a stretch so we are conveniently
parked outside the Starbucks let's see
if we can get Wi-Fi
oh well long ago guest:i networks here
yeah real Starbucks guys we weren't
lying absolutely Starbucks no we should
have probably tested to see if we could
you know connect to the oh but I like
back when we were at the house like
gigabit internet yeah yeah very
reasonable oh shit well now it's just
because I have a I have an IP address
let's just switch this convenient thing
back to you with DHCP cuz this is real
shit though
and that's why hopefully you appreciate
my streams I would never lie to you all
I was going to Safari let's see if we
can get on get up you are not connected
to the Internet you are not connected to
the unit
why am I not welcome github doesn't work
from your tether whoa there's a chance
we can tether to her we dolphin that'll
work now that I fixed the IP address
issue and a nun crashed okay we're in we
let see everything
around the host
work I actually don't have to get to my
computer if I can just get to github
we're good
Oh get up work sorry perfect
so let's just go in here to our secret
repository yeah maybe we maybe we don't
show mr. down you get to see the Aeon
you get to see the Aeon art so let's see
um so I just download this key oh wow
that's actually the private key yeah I
don't I
we have a key hey let's just try this
kid SSH - nai drsa we control the screen
again alright let's connect to wheedle
estate CID RSA or 80 22 and now we're
gonna do well we don't even need to be
parked here we can go back to where you
are yeah let's go buy Starbucks five
star marks a d'Artagnan and add I'll be
back for my free coffee well actually
let's see if we can SSH in first hey
blend in perfect kid they're gonna take
a customer here and be like look at the
beautiful car we got for sale well they
are lockboxes on all the other ones just
have the keys in them so if you guys
want to steal a lot of Corollas don't
say that file too short what
- pile to shore oh I see they're faster
because you don't use the capital I use
the lowercase
bad permission that's fine so I can just
chamalla at 600 600 IDR I said come on
Connect connect connect oh yeah we're
connected to the Aeon guys but we are
now connected to a neon and it's waiting
for DFU that's why the pandas fought so
let's just um fuck the Panda me a second
yeah say somewhere according to George
quote George Hobbes advocates for
stealing cars some tech magazine great
flashing guys some hackers shit alright
let's try it again this we're in last
alright alright it's goin opening panda
no wait why does it have an old version
huh make her copper boys be not in not
in we're not in voice they all got
really excited cover all right don't
worry I'm making recover I can't it's a
friend oh shit I didn't bring a pause so
if I fuck this up that's it
oh if you break it you're fog if I break
it I'm fucked a cop t fu you birthday oh
no the new knee OS doesn't have d fu
util oh oh god C it is because we have
weird eons
okay wait I'm can I access the internet
from the C on I can't we just have to
download DF your you tell from the old
me OS okay so DF your util is a tool
that talks raw mode to the processor the
problem is we updated me OS internally
which is the internal build of the neo
operating system which actually this bug
doesn't affect anybody else in the world
just us internally the question is
everyone's everyone's doing that
emoticon with two hands on their head
the question is where the hell am I
going to get a DF you util under short
notice are we
um they're disappoint yeah yeah yeah
okay so if somebody could extract from
the OS the da-fu util that has a
reasonable we do it live guys we do it
live all right
no actually I know where it is I know
where it is we can download it quickly I
have the perfect place for it just I
need your hot spot again it's still up
no I turned off no it isn't it is it
isn't really your internet it never
turns off no it does even no one's
connected you bro
still fucking on stays on toggle your
Wi-Fi the problem is when you buy a new
panda this bug is also gonna be fixed
with the July first hardware the problem
is moving buy a new panda the I know
exactly where the file is on github we
just have to get it so give up that
comms I not be sure I'm get our back on
size coming Isis user this is all public
so we have to go in we have to find DFU
you tell and then maybe
in DFU okay we just got to searching
this repo for DFU you tell I think it
has to be in here so that's been maybe
no local someone said just do got cloned
EFT util got clone got close yeah make
sure there's got it
I found okay so wait let me just copy
this download link so we can actually
download it right here on the eon but
actually we're not connected to the eon
anymore so let's download it on my
computer to make double sure okay we
have DF you you tell on my computer
let's go over to we'd all oh yeah
fuck that we tool up yeah and we can't
see the problem is we can't connect to
both all right so we're back connected
to the phone now let's just go in and
we're gonna curl that you are being
redirected what is curl to follow
redirects alt and then we'll say o DF
Naruto what it couldn't write the file
right
um all right we're downloading could not
resolve host DFU Utah is that not what o
is for or we have a faculty of Utah
let's run it
oh yeah right we got to give you you
tell all right now I just need to mount
actually a system already mounted they
go to system bin can I touch something
here right now - Oh remount RW system MV
1 DF you you tell here mount - OH ro
system me recover all right fingers
crossed guys cuz if I fuck this up we're
just done no I didn't fuck it off I
don't know why that's failing well cuz
the pandas in that mode
pottery was true
she's not entering bootlegger let's just
power cycle the Panda
you know we can do we can just turn the
car off and unplug that and then we plug
that back in let you power the pan to
back up did
make torque up
okay good good good win-win-win look at
that shit we're downloading
this is some real hacker shit guys oh
fuck yeah all right mainframe breached
mainframe priests right so now let's
just restart manager right here oh my
god and we already did the SS aging so
the fingerprinting is gonna be easy
we're gonna be up on the road in 15
minutes if everything else works real
life hacker shit this is real life
hacker shit guys cuz you mic our next
manager cool so it's booting yeah don't
call yeah Mel dot load guys it's booting
up Oh
so restarting everything now I'm the EON
who wants to take bets on if he bricks
it I'll take a line on that I'll give
odds wait all right so I think we're
connected now okay let's just try Pat
booting the car and now it should
hopefully if I didn't fuck anything else
up go to started mode Oh guys did you
fuck the we don't know okay okay yeah
notice how we're in dashcam mode with
unsupported car right now yeah this is
actually okay we're just gonna need to
add a fingerprint which is gonna be less
annoying and I hope calibration process
yeah yeah it's got a calibrated but
so there's a tool in self-drive debug
called get fingerprint let's just get
the fingerprint for the car I think this
works alright perfect this is the
fingerprint this easel this is the
fingerprint of the Corolla ecstasy it's
public knowledge you got alright because
we're gonna add it we're gonna push it
right now alright so now we just got to
go into one self-drive where the
fingerprints go in like saw your cables
probably part of your family that's
right oh yeah we will fix that in a
minute
get grap fingerprints where are the
fingerprints oh it's in let's just go in
here to car Toyota values yeah yeah here
they are alright so we have a Corolla
we're just gonna mm see okay the only
one we actually support here is the O
rav4 2019 I say you know what for now
let's just hack it and add it to the
Corolla hatch the same car we actually
don't support the 2020 coral which is
copy and paste this fingerprint into
this convenient Python file here
now let's restart manager and hopefully
we're not going to get any more dashcam
bullshit in before we get some more
dashcam bullshit if we get more - damn
bullshit we'll fix it because we're
genius hackers ok starting manager these
guys saw this last time don't break it
I'm not gonna break it don't work no
Paul no Panda Paul no we have no Paul
vez no no we're past where we could
break it
okay guys successfully reflashed if we
had unplugged it not like a split second
there's a chance we would have break
down now that would have been
devastating okay good
we rebooted we're connected to the Panda
everything looks good can't see ya know
I can't ever get we go good let's go no
dashcam oh it works out are you gonna
kill me no stack em up why is it in
dashcam
Oh
it shouldn't be in - camera let's just
look at the code and see what's
happening by the way you're running chat
story is that you you stole a car from
Toyota you're trying to hack a flaw
perfect now let's get advice to run that
a hat should have that where is - down
mode and when do we go into us when do
we choose - but notice how it doesn't
say anymore that it's uh this is
probably just because we have weird
internal controls live alerts so I'm
just looking reducing the screen this is
pretty good this is useful it's a wind -
come out so this is when it's throwing
an alert of startup no control so that's
happening here
startup no control and not controller
available why is there no controller
available maybe there's some other thing
and not understanding get startup alert
so this is a new stuff that's going to
be in a pilot pretty soon control
ah CP an able camera and not passive so
what's enable camera oh I think it's
just in I have the switches in a wrong
orientation
I think that you just might have to flip
a switch
I think think that that that that thing
was wrong all the twitches wrong
I think the twitches were wrong damn it
twitches no let's uh you want shit your
dirty screen really triggered a lot of
people by the way what thirty scran yoga
laptop oh I'm terribly sorry
um wait I think it's the switches I
think maybe would try switch to and not
switch one or something
maybe that'll work they said if we were
wrong that means you were wrong so they
copied it from the first oh wait I think
we're good I think we're good
yeah don't trust any of the posts guys
guys don't trust any of the post cuz
it's wrong it was wrong the post lied oh
yeah everyone's seatbelts on
I let's go are you ready to take over at
any time I always keep hands on the
wheel alright alright I'm gonna have to
calibrate it we chose down for it dog
let's get on the highway and go open
pile-driving hi this is a completely
untested car nobody has ever driven a
2020 Corolla before but we just did some
extreme hacking why Packer man yes you
can drives it off look out it's a hacker
man you back my cars here ya know just
we're just gonna go for a quick spin on
the highway and confirm that we're using
the greatest self-driving system
available for a Toyota Corolla this is a
brand new Corolla how long did that take
us how long from its dreaming flat yeah
I don't know how long and how long that
took oh wait do I have to show my
license yeah I don't think so you bought
the car walk the car that's right yeah
no just drive let's go oh this guy
bought a new car too but he doesn't know
how to drive he's gonna like take
forever to second 40 minutes 37 minutes
38 minutes 38 minutes so that's how long
it takes to set up a new open pilot
all right we just gotta wait for the
calibration to finish up here it's
pretty fast it's got to drive above 60
miles an hour if you guys saw that movie
speed it's just like that oh the movie
with the flaming boss yeah yeah it's
just like that yeah yeah yeah I feel
bright like I'm on the flaming bus right
now
all right this is a brand new Corolla we
just installed I'll compile it in it we
finally I hopefully got the switches in
the right orientation I'm happy we
didn't start hacking the code to fix
that that was incredible - cam oh I wish
it actually told you that your switches
were in the wrong orientation I mean
that would be nice but like you know you
can't expect a lot this is beta software
always beta software oh I can't engage
because my calibrations not done we have
to finish the calibration first
oh yeah we're only at 30 right 30 so
this is right now for sale on shop
account a TI for $5.99 and you can buy
one always plug always plug yeah always
all right so we're going at a decent
speed here for calibrating thing I think
we got away yeah they're still driving
this is the same route the guy took us
on right how do I get to that highway to
go oh it's down here on the right yeah
you turn to the KFC car ready oh your
stream cut out or something and just got
back at what uh oh they're good oh
that's a good point we're we're like
streaming
60 62 64 66 let's get in there yes yes
the car was legitimately purchased there
was an invoice to prove I know he's not
a law requires wasn't a joke
he was driving this car back to San
Diego in an hour it's got a p.m. days
gotta be there Oh
cable in front of the camera oh fuck all
right moment of truth
okay there you go let's give it a shot
radar crews active cruise control
malfunction visit your dealer get fogged
yeah oh yeah it just gives me a
concussion
dude good lord now it's fine nothing's
as rough as a Ferrari that is true
right sure all oh shit what fun ways
call this out man we swapped cars which
is which is chella near the wheel is
really show the wheel look at that
2020 Corolla aunty 20 Corolla only 2011
52 minutes 52 minutes to set up a new
product that changes your iPad do a
quick spin on the highway and then drop
this guy back off at the dealership I'm
then you're going to San Diego to San
Diego and I'm not Streamwood I'm not
bringing you twitches with me I'm sorry
this is wait it lost it
no yeah freeway right here how about the
torque house pretty good how many people
we got good 99 oh wait we lost hundreds
of people yeah they'll come back
hundreds of people think I died yeah
thank you other people think you
probably died guys this is so little in
your life can be the difference between
a complete success and a total failure
and now hundreds of people will go away
and think of me as a total failure and I
will never be able to recapture that
audience
yeah famous last words what was it
dealer it what auto lane keep assist
malfunction
a good thing we got the sport mode maybe
that works right yeah good thing you pay
for that 430 horsepower pay for the
extra 30 horsepower guys we did that
live that could have gone so much worse
you know see
oh don't worry someone said they thought
you were a failure before tonight well
you're probably right all right we were
on a beautiful Los Angeles I don't even
see any of you can't see anything to the
ER not see or you mean them no me yeah
let's just get over to this lead right
here we're gonna just press this button
- let's see how it works cool guys
the flame arts or shit
no hands no hands speed up a little bit
I heard there was a song about that look
ma no hands I mean that one I can drive
my car with no they say can you please
turn back so you don't stare okay I
won't point it at the Sun then you can't
see it your mom it's still coming oh
there we go such about
these lanes are pretty crap
someone said what the fuck happened - no
comment hey I on twitch this is the one
day we broke that rule guys we broke
that rule for the love of a brand-new
Toyota Corolla normally there's no
comments what you know what that's a
good rule and we're gonna leave the
stream right there my my twenties bite
which is how I ended Oh bite to it
cheese Oh how's the Instagram dream he's
gonna be there soon bastard
yes here
Hansol phone
et of yours
so the lateral needs a little bit of
tuning you can see it's ping-pong a tiny
bit in the lane that's because the 2020
Corolla is an unsupported car and we
just added support for today in the
other live stream which was pretty
insane
the problem with leaving you at that
other stream it gives you the impression
that open pilot is like mostly getting
into work
but that's not true it's mostly chilling
while you drive
I don't know we see and this is another
thing to thank you thank you and this is
another thing to like Arnott which
dreams about kama AI they're not they're
not like the periscopes when I was on
the periscopes you know I would like to
talk about self-driving car companies
the twitch tombs are about my life and
driving back from San Diego with old
pilot was kind of just a part of my life
in here we are
I don't know why we only have Turkey
viewers are where the viewers would
because the streams crappy something
drive back Sandiego
it's because I'm an crap you know that's
useful
this is the appropriate ending for the
video
the appropriate ending for the video is
just watching open pilot drive down the
road
it's my legit drive back to San Diego I
have a date at 8 p.m. tonight just
barely gonna make it
Oh what it took to get it working was
literally just turning the car off and
on again the problem is it's because I
didn't turn the car fully off when we
were sitting there I had the air
conditioner running because we were
sitting in the car and it was cold
I wanted to be called so I didn't turn
the car fully off after I reset it so I
just turned it off going again
you saw the hard stuff
you know real dog is one time I was in I
was in Korea and I was giving a talk and
this was probably the precursor to live
streams and I was at like a Korean
Spotify and I hacked their DRM onstage
in front of them but I didn't get the
last part done
I got the last part done 20 minutes
later when I was on the train it was
kind of devastating because I could have
kept going and I would have had it done
all right 28 minutes but here we are
we're cruising I show you both hands but
the other ones holding the phone they
bring a mount
so always keep your eyes on the road
when you're using any one of these
systems their level two
as long as you keep your eyes on the
rain pretty king
I don't know
I'm old guys mamas 30
take road trips across the country was
great time to reflect
Oh Oh the faster
[Music]
yeah shoutouts to come AI archive when
you're uploading this now stitch the
three parts together
this is an appropriate last 10 minutes
now how about we don't talk about that
many I because we have to talk about
coming out because it is part of my life
and that's the struggle right
everyone's brand these days
it's joke
yeah it's an actuator I bought it today
at the dealership we hacked it in the
dealership parking lot
we're just gonna cruise we'll leave the
stream on on the view of perception
all the software that you see here is
open-source
github.com / compromise / open pilot
you know check it out
a little hard just need to connect a few
bar top
the physical installation took five
minutes the bug in the software that's
not in the publicly released version
took 20 and then adding the fingerprint
took another 10 and then realizing I had
to reboot the car to 10
Travel and outdoors traveling I thought
it was an appropriate category No
so yeah you can see that my eyes are and
on you guys have a second they might
make mistakes I think we're going about
20 minutes now without mistake hope they
do make mistakes they're very small
minor mistakes
make driving shelf
excess thank you I hope you are healthy
and wealthy as well
unless you made your wealth by taking it
from others
and then in which case I hope you go
broke I'm sure you're not that kind of
guy
it's very similar so this car right now
isn't tuned to the best so it's a little
it's a bit underperforming autopilot you
see this little bit of ping pong in the
lanes but this is a brand new car we
bought it today so this is just the out
of the box with a new unsupported car
after we tuned it and we're gonna spend
a week tuning it it's gonna be it's on
par with autopilot it's kind of
different
um autopilot is a little more almost
aggressive and how they like market
things and want to do things
big targets
and we used to have a six minute timeout
so it used to be every six minutes you
needed to touch the wheel but now if you
see this little icon here the little
icon in the lower left corner that means
that open pilot is watching me and
making sure they're not keeping my eyes
on the road as long as you are you can
cruise forever
I don't want babies scare me
No
you know who stops to think about things
that they did bitches and work and do
anything else always be thinking about
what you're gonna do next
always thinking about how you're gonna
be better even as I decline into my 30s
and you really think people decline in
their 30s actually made in the 40s and
I'm 30
I don't know we can look at my face
we're gonna look at the wheel we can
look at the Aeon I kind of got three
shots
I'll get eclis try to read your chats
this is the real open pilot experience
Gus you set it up it's frantic it's
exciting
and then
there's a song
I like
and one of the lines so we just drive
wide eye and full of spots I like
traffic driving high I've driven across
the country alone a bunch of times gives
you time to reflect
world but not unlike what you've done
right like that's kind of off
don't you ever start thinking about like
old what I did was so great like what
I'm gonna do is so great you know
I've been able to auto lane change now I
mean so auto lane change the problem
with auto lane change is
and I just I just lost the chat see if I
can get it back show chat the chat with
auto lane change
is this car can probably do it actually
combined with I wouldn't want to add an
auto lane change until the car could
automatically make sure the lane change
was safe and right now we don't have all
the hardware required to do that but
it's really easy to do I don't know I
could do a lane change guys but I
haven't touched the wheel in 30 minutes
I don't really want to
just chill it changes our chill
hey baby that's the difference you don't
pollen autopilot you know in a way like
autopilot it's like look at this cool
gimmicky technology and I mean yeah sure
if you're Tesla and you're trying to
like sell cars that meeting quota Wow my
insulting test lawn here I don't need to
do that I don't mean to do that I have
nothing but love it's a different
product because
they they're pushing like navigator
autopilot and they're talking about full
self-driving what I'm talking about is
to take the driving experience of
millions of say Americans and make it
just more chill make it more relaxing
you don't have to adjust the car
thousands of times per minute I think as
I got an average the driver does like to
actions of seconds 1:28 p.m. or I don't
know how often you turn it maybe it's
less than that but still it's certainly
multiple times a minute
it's uh needed work and stress
yeah the rule for a violin is if it
doesn't make driving more chill it
doesn't go in 120 APM
at 70 here
this is the new model now this is to
Paris Kofi this is to periscoping we're
not we're not talking about that it's
the white female month tomorrow mild and
well model coming
cars gonna cut in here we're going to
slow down a tiny bit
fine
I always kind of wall you know
tiny bit of pink on that wheel
what will save VR I don't know
if you ask me if you can ask a question
the answer is gone if you just ask the
question I'll read it and decide whether
I've entertained by it or not
but yeah right now if you're on
if you ever support a car and you're on
highway like this you don't need to do
anything anymore except pay attention
most of the time
maybe once an hour you have to do
something
so if we stream for now I'm sure you'll
see me have to take one like corrective
action
we usually chill things Cotton's are
calming
really poorly painted thing lines
[Music]
thank you ma'am
this cars got a moonroof let's place me
this is a sunroof
he's bigger
[Music]
smile
we're us as we travel away to some
basement we do it for the sentiments it
started with a self asserted promise
I will be okay everything
muumuus has solid cloth cover know when
I'm answering questions about combi I
guys this is just my life that's the
difference
periscope was about comedy I and we
don't do that anymore comedy was a real
company me as George Hotz
there's not really a wedge rather be
coming back from LA right now
I wish the tuning was a little bit
better effects like this week
you know you guys like yeah I don't know
we don't either talk on the way down
here about what's genuine and what's not
being genuine is really important to me
but not signalling that I'm genuine
right because if those two things are
different
if being genuine is signalling that you
are genuine that this is phenomenon in
society day of like truthiness things
that feel true but aren't that or
sometime they feel more true than the
truth and this is a problem if I'm ever
not genuine I don't do it for you I do
it for me
people say that on these two extremes to
like you know if you put time and effort
into planning his content it would be so
much better maybe but I don't do it for
you I do it for me
but I do it for me for you do you see
what I mean
like em I was trying to optimize if
there was a way that I decided like I'm
not gonna be myself I'm not gonna be
myself because that would increase view
numbers that's worthless to me because
the moment you've given that up the
moment you've given up actually being
yourself and not having people believe
that you are yourself you're a worthless
piece of shit until of course you know
and like like it's not saying if you
ever did this right like everyone's been
in the scenario where they were
uncomfortable and act in a way that
wasn't like that but there are people I
see who do this all the time why be
whoever you are
and accepting you don't know why I mean
you gotta find who you are but yeah too
long of a rant it sounds like a song
from frozen right what's that what's
that oh no it's from Book of Mormon are
you and me but mostly ever since I was a
child I tried to be the best so what
happened my family and friends all said
I was blessed so what happens it was
supposed to be all so exciting to be
teaching of Christ cross the sea but I
allowed my faith to be shaken oh what's
the matter with me I always longed to
help the needy to do the things I never
dared that was the chance for me to step
up so then why was I so scared a warlord
who shoots people in the face what's so
scary about that I must trust that my
Lord is mightier and always has my back
all right
should we do the course
who knows the song guys it's a great
play by the way if you haven't seen
Book of Mormon I've been watching plays
on YouTube lately but I would be happy
to pay someone money for that content if
they made that good but I'm not gonna
like fly somewhere like I watch like
what do i watch i watch the if then I'd
be a Manzo I'm nobody's her it was her
understudy was Jackie who was the girl
death I started to watch next to normal
but I got bored
[Music]
so we got some you see with zip and by
these cars on the left here so you gotta
we've got to pay extra attention
that's doing fine far away or Apple just
what do what do you think I'm American
you know I love China but I'm an
American
and apples a good company I bought a
home pod recently I'm just thinking
because I think nice to get about like
how an Apple did USBC and how that's a
lot of that is largely thanks to Apple
Apple pioneered removing floppy drives
or moving cd-rom drives and they have
enough almost authority in the industry
to doing it when Apple comes out with
something it's good I respect them I
respect their business model god I said
the same thing years ago about Google
now but you gotta just look at the
business model if the business model is
not consumer aligned it doesn't matter
how a line do you think the founders
might be like it doesn't matter how cool
you think Larry and Sergey are and how
they want to do good things for the
world
if their business model is is that just
showing the wheel well I don't know
Highway Patrol
we've got another I've got another 50
minutes drive
what about hype around interfacing with
the brain
you know is there hype around that now
you want to learn Kali Linux Oh kitty
hawk the little flying thingies is that
what these are I mean that's what the
periscopes used to be just Shutt talking
companies I don't know I wish everybody
the best except for the people who get
up every day and make the world worse
and I wish that they would you know die
no I mean okay you know the people who
genuinely get up and are like you know
what we are gonna get this new
regulation passed that is going to make
filling out tax forms for Americans
three times more complicated but at the
same time we're gonna sell them our
software they're evil like if you're
making people's lives worse you're evil
if you're like like like like I'm going
to create a problem for you and then
provide the solution like the model of
crack dealers you know I'm gonna provide
the problem for you which is crack
addiction but I'm gonna provide the
solution which is crack oh yeah look at
how smoothly it deals with those
transitions oh we're losing the lanes
here all right good job open pilot good
job good yawn I pet the EON but
phone
we'll cut in right there did it right if
you take the hob Lane
you take a half
I can't really read chat cuz I don't
have a mountain fortunately I'll hold it
here chat some tiny Thanks TurboTax
right
any good Callie or I don't know all
right guys no say I wanted to show a
genuine experience of what open pilot is
like not just the set of experience
so hopefully this gets tacked onto the
end of the video comment AI archive